questions = [{'timestamps': '11/05/2022 14:40:58'}, {'question': 'How can I get a list of sheets (name and "gid") in a Google spreadsheet using the Drive API?', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/32642244', 'summary': "I am trying to use Google Drive API (Python) to download some tabs of a spreadsheets file. Are the gids information in the file's metadata? What I am trying to do is (this may not be correct, please ...", 'answers': '2', 'votes': '27', 'tags': 'python python-2.7 google-drive-api google-api-python-client'}, {'question': 'Pygame Xbox One Controller', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/49887874', 'summary': 'I am trying to run some code that will allow the user to control with an Xbox Controller. I have it working with the Xbox 360 controller using Pygame. Then when I try to use the Xbox one controller ...', 'answers': '1', 'votes': '27', 'tags': 'python pygame'}, {'question': 'Joblib UserWarning while trying to cache results', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/37129754', 'summary': 'I get the following UserWarning when trying to cache results using joblib: from tempfile import mkdtemp cachedir = mkdtemp() from joblib import Memory memory = Memory(cachedir=cachedir, verbose=0) @...', 'answers': 0, 'votes': '26', 'tags': 'python numpy netcdf joblib'}, {'question': 'Parallely running parameterized tests in pytest', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/29560212', 'summary': 'I wanted to run parameterized test functions in parallel. This is for a concurrency testing scenario. Same testcase runs in parallel with different parameters in a device. After completing all the ...', 'answers': '1', 'votes': '26', 'tags': 'python pytest'}, {'question': 'Keras layer with int inputs cannot be built', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/56786328', 'summary': 'I have a complex keras model in which one of the layers is a custom pretrained layer which expects "int32" as inputs. This model is implemented as a class that inherits from Model and it is ...', 'answers': '1', 'votes': '25', 'tags': 'python class keras'}, {'question': 'Locust.io Load Testing getting "Connection aborted BadStatusLine" Errors', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/31600508', 'summary': 'I\'m using Locust.io to load test an application. I will get a random error that I am unable to pinpoint the problem: 1) ConnectionError(ProtocolError(\\\'Connection aborted.\\\', BadStatusLine("\\\'\\\'&...', 'answers': '1', 'votes': '25', 'tags': 'python server python-requests locust'}, {'question': 'Matplotlib in Rmarkdown/RStudio fails when calling LaTeX on `\\$` with Anaconda', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/58502671', 'summary': 'Problem description I am having to use Anaconda on Windows, and am trying to write an RMarkdown document, knitted into a pdf, where within the RMarkdown I am using some Python snippets. However, when ...', 'answers': 0, 'votes': '23', 'tags': 'python r matplotlib latex r-markdown'}, {'question': 'Flask app with ArcGIS, Arcpy does not run', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/51292905', 'summary': 'I have a script that gets a table from MSSQL database and then registers it with ArcGIS. It uses several other arcpy methods as well. I tried to combine it with Flask and developed an HTML interface ...', 'answers': '2', 'votes': '23', 'tags': 'python flask arcpy pymssql'}, {'question': 'The correct bone data to export from blender to view in ogl?', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/6129866', 'summary': 'Edit (Original post below): So I have come up with the following code. I can export the mesh, bone structure and animations. I can animate a simple skeleton. But for some reason if I animate more ...', 'answers': '1', 'votes': '22', 'tags': 'python math animation blender blender-2.50'}, {'question': 'using randomized_svd for recommendation', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/37290677', 'summary': 'I was following paper : Effective Latent Models for Binary Feedback in Recommender Systems by Maksims N. Volkovs and Guang Wei Yu. It is for producing recommendation using model based approach, SVD by ...', 'answers': 0, 'votes': '21', 'tags': 'python scikit-learn sparse-matrix'}, {'question': 'Execute multiple independent statements in SQLAlchemy Core?', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/37288420', 'summary': "I'm using SQLAlchemy Core to run a few independent statements. The statements are to separate tables and unrelated. Because of that I can't use the standard table.insert() with multiple dictionaries ...", 'answers': '1', 'votes': '21', 'tags': 'python mysql sqlalchemy'}, {'question': 'Change loss function dynamically during training in Keras, without recompiling other model properties like optimizer', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/55979176', 'summary': 'Is it possible to set model.loss in a callback without re-compiling model.compile(...) after (since then the optimizer states are reset), and just recompiling model.loss, like for example: class ...', 'answers': '1', 'votes': '20', 'tags': 'python keras callback epoch loss'}, {'question': 'Tesseract OCR confuses slashed 0 as 8', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/53090447', 'summary': "I have trained tesseract on the terminus font, but no matter what, I can't get it to recognize the 0s. I am using the jTessEditor to create the training tif and boxes. Even when validating, it reads ...", 'answers': '2', 'votes': '20', 'tags': 'python ocr tesseract'}, {'question': 'Train Stacked Autoencoder Correctly', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/52221103', 'summary': 'I try to build a Stacked Autoencoder in Keras (tf.keras). By stacked I do not mean deep. All the examples I found for Keras are generating e.g. 3 encoder layers, 3 decoder layers, they train it and ...', 'answers': '1', 'votes': '20', 'tags': 'python tensorflow machine-learning keras deep-learning'}, {'question': "Decoder's weights of Autoencoder with tied weights in Keras", 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/42015116', 'summary': 'I have implemented a tied weights Auto-encoder in Keras and have successfully trained it. My goal is to use only the decoder part of the Auto-encoder as the last layer of another network, to fine ...', 'answers': '1', 'votes': '20', 'tags': 'python machine-learning neural-network keras autoencoder'}, {'question': 'Why is reversed(mylist) so slow?', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/60005302', 'summary': "(Update: Might only happen in CPython 3.8 32-bit for Windows, so don't be surprised if you can't reproduce it in other versions. See tables in the Update section.) Both iter and reversed result in ...", 'answers': '1', 'votes': '20', 'tags': 'python performance 64-bit 32-bit'}, {'question': 'AWS Fargate Task - awslogs driver - Intermittent Logs', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/54084601', 'summary': 'I am running a one-off Fargate Task that runs a small python script. The Task Definition is configured to use awslogs to send logs to Cloudwatch but I am facing a very strange intermittent issue. ...', 'answers': '2', 'votes': '19', 'tags': 'python docker python-asyncio amazon-ecs aiohttp'}, {'question': 'pygame multithread client socket GUI Blocking', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/52607405', 'summary': "I wanna write a gomoku game with server and client, the terminal version works good, but pygame version just blocked and can't rend anything Here is the game execute function First it start a socket ...", 'answers': 0, 'votes': '18', 'tags': 'python sockets user-interface pygame blocking'}, {'question': 'Python using gattlib for BLE Scanning on Windows 10', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/49238744', 'summary': 'I want to create a BLE Connection between my Laptop (Windows 10) and a BLE Device which will be the Master. I installed Bluez and I can detect Bluetooth devices like my Smartphone but no device that ...', 'answers': '2', 'votes': '18', 'tags': 'python windows-10 bluetooth-lowenergy'}, {'question': 'Avoid restarting Jupyter kernel in package develop mode?', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/47902297', 'summary': 'I am working on a python package as a developer. The package is stored in a git repo and I use a local branch to debug/fix this package. I use Jupyter notebooks using pip in edit mode to load my local ...', 'answers': '4', 'votes': '18', 'tags': 'python python-3.x pip jupyter-notebook'}, {'question': 'ANTLR4 Python parsing big files', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/35929426', 'summary': "I am trying to write parsers for juniper/srx router access control lists. Below is the grammar I am using: grammar SRXBackend; acl: 'security' '{' 'policies' '{' COMMENT* replaceStmt '{' policy* ...", 'answers': '1', 'votes': '18', 'tags': 'python parsing antlr antlr4'}, {'question': "OS X cmake can't find PythonLibs 3.4", 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/30470628', 'summary': 'python and python3 are installed in OS X Yosemite via Homebrew, but cmake fails to find PythonLibs 3, only 2: CMakeLists.txt: set(Python_ADDITIONAL_VERSIONS 3.4) FIND_PACKAGE(PythonInterp REQUIRED) ...', 'answers': '2', 'votes': '18', 'tags': 'python macos python-3.x cmake'}, {'question': 'Workaround for TypeVar bound on a TypeVar?', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/57590086', 'summary': "Is there some way of expressing this Scala code with Python's type hints? trait List[A] { def ::[B >: A](x: B): List[B] } I'm trying to achieve this sort of thing class X: pass class Y(X): pass ...", 'answers': '1', 'votes': '18', 'tags': 'python types type-hinting type-bounds'}, {'question': 'How to ignore the dependencies of a specific package when installing it with pipenv?', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/51046150', 'summary': "Is there a possibility to install a python package with pipenv without also installing the dependencies? I'm looking for an analogue of pip install package_name --no-dependencies for the Pipfile. I ...", 'answers': '1', 'votes': '17', 'tags': 'python pipenv'}, {'question': 'Set column order in alembic when adding a new column', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/50601917', 'summary': "I'm struggling to find a clean way (without raw SQL) to set the column order in alembic. For example, I would like to put a new column called 'name' after the 'id' column, something like this: from ...", 'answers': '1', 'votes': '16', 'tags': 'python sqlalchemy database-migration alembic'}, {'question': 'Python Requests: IOError: [Errno 22] Invalid argument', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/35466918', 'summary': 'I am new to Python Requests and am encountering an IOError:[Errno 22] Invalid argument when I attempt a requests.get(). In short, I am attempting to connect to an internal web application using SSL ...', 'answers': '1', 'votes': '16', 'tags': 'python ssl python-requests urllib3'}, {'question': '"ModuleNotFoundError: No module named \'pysqlcipher3\'" error while using Python 3.7 on windows 10', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/54128295', 'summary': 'I am trying to decrypt one database file using Python 3.7. To decrypt it, I have to use pysqlcipher3 version for python 3.7. To install it, I have tried by using both commands: pip3 install ...', 'answers': '8', 'votes': '16', 'tags': 'python python-3.x pysqlcipher'}, {'question': 'bson.errors.InvalidDocument: Cannot encode object: True', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/23169728', 'summary': "I got an error when inserting a document in Mongo using python. document = {u'Status': 'Active', u'Installation': {u'IsFrugal': True, u'IsFeatureSet': True, u'IsEvolving': True, u'...", 'answers': '2', 'votes': '16', 'tags': 'python python-2.7 pymongo'}, {'question': "mach-o file, but is an incompatible architecture have 'x86_64', need 'arm64e' M1 MAC", 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/70099893', 'summary': 'from PyQt6.QtWidgets import * from model.Department import Department from view.main_window import Ui_Form from model.Department import Department, Employee class Homewidget(QWidget,Ui_Form): ...', 'answers': '1', 'votes': '15', 'tags': 'python arm64 apple-m1 mach-o pyqt6'}, {'question': 'Python AVRO reader returns AssertionError when decoding kafka messages', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/58473110', 'summary': 'Newbie playing with Kafka and AVRO. I am trying to deserialise AVRO messages in Python 3.7.3 using kafka-python, avro-python3 packages and following this answer. The function responsible for ...', 'answers': '1', 'votes': '15', 'tags': 'python avro kafka-python'}, {'question': 'How to apply oversampling when doing Leave-One-Group-Out cross validation?', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/56964533', 'summary': 'I am working on an imbalanced data for classification and I tried to use Synthetic Minority Over-sampling Technique (SMOTE) previously to oversampling the training data. However, this time I think I ...', 'answers': '1', 'votes': '15', 'tags': 'python machine-learning scikit-learn cross-validation imblearn'}, {'question': '`tiny_malloc_from_free_list` made my pointer `NULL`?', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/51654074', 'summary': 'I am working on code that includes bllipparser Python module, among other things. Feeding it the same dataset, it will intermittently crash (maybe once in three to ten runs). Going through lldb, I ...', 'answers': '1', 'votes': '15', 'tags': 'python macos memory-management lldb bllip-parser'}, {'question': 'Jupyter notebook show and capture output at the same time', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/49524626', 'summary': 'I\'m trying to figure out a way to "save" the variables in a jupyter notebook but also capture the rich output at the same time. Mainly for reasons of ssh disconnecting, etc. Just assigning to ...', 'answers': '1', 'votes': '15', 'tags': 'python ipython jupyter-notebook'}, {'question': 'Tree-LSTM in Keras', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/46758489', 'summary': 'I would like to use a tree-LSTM in keras, similar to what is described in this article: https://arxiv.org/abs/1503.00075. It is essentially similar to a Long Short-Term Memory network, but with a tree-...', 'answers': '1', 'votes': '15', 'tags': 'python deep-learning keras lstm'}, {'question': 'Attention Layer throwing TypeError: Permute layer does not support masking in Keras', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/45691644', 'summary': 'I have been following this post in order to implement attention layer over my LSTM model. Code for the attention layer: INPUT_DIM = 2 TIME_STEPS = 20 SINGLE_ATTENTION_VECTOR = False ...', 'answers': '1', 'votes': '15', 'tags': 'python tensorflow keras lstm attention-model'}, {'question': "robobrowser won't change cookies", 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/45467986', 'summary': "I have a POST request sent to server from robobrowser, and the server responds with no data. The response headers are as follows (this is the response from Chrome browser and it's the way it supposed ...", 'answers': 0, 'votes': '15', 'tags': 'python python-2.7 http python-requests urllib2'}, {'question': 'Dealing with Concurrent Requests & Connections in Cloud SQL', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/35043927', 'summary': 'We have created an app on App Engine using Datastore. Now we have been led to using Cloud SQL as we wanted to use joins, nested queries and functions such as average, total etc. Data gets migrated ...', 'answers': 0, 'votes': '15', 'tags': 'python mysql google-app-engine google-cloud-sql'}, {'question': 'mpiexec and python mpi4py gives rank 0 and size 1', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/29264640', 'summary': 'I have a problem with running a python Hello World mpi4py code on a virtual machine. The hello.py code is: #!/usr/bin/python #hello.py from mpi4py import MPI comm = MPI.COMM_WORLD size = comm....', 'answers': '2', 'votes': '15', 'tags': 'python mpi mpi4py mpiexec'}, {'question': 'How can I debug "Exception while resolving variable in template \'unknown\'"?', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/43663877', 'summary': "I keep seeing DEBUG Exception while resolving variable 'exception_type' in template 'unknown'. in my django logs, followed by VariableDoesNotExist: Failed lookup for key [exception_type] in ...", 'answers': '1', 'votes': '15', 'tags': 'python django django-templates'}, {'question': 'Does Poetry have an equivalent for the flag "--trusted-host" that is available on Pip?', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/70104516', 'summary': 'I wish to start using poetry on some projects at work, where I am stuck behind corporate filters that sometimes interfere with certs. If I use pip, I can ignore SSL errors by doing something like the ...', 'answers': 0, 'votes': '14', 'tags': 'python python-3.x python-poetry pyproject.toml'}, {'question': 'Is it possible to write a luigi wrapper task that tolerates failed sub-tasks?', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/61596529', 'summary': 'I have a luigi task that performs some non-stable computations. Think of an optimization process that sometimes does not converge. import luigi MyOptimizer(luigi.Task): input_param: luigi....', 'answers': 0, 'votes': '14', 'tags': 'python error-handling dataflow luigi data-pipeline'}, {'question': 'Is there a way in matplotlib to check which artists are in the currently displayed area of the axes?', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/60263459', 'summary': 'I have a program with an interactive figure where occasionally many artists are drawn. In this figure, you can also zoom and pan using the mouse. However, the performace during zooming an panning is ...', 'answers': '1', 'votes': '14', 'tags': 'python performance matplotlib'}, {'question': 'Conda create env from file - How to specify prefix in the file?', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/59392454', 'summary': 'I read that the prefix line in the environment.yaml file is not used by conda env create. Two of the posts on SO pointing to this fact are: export conda environment without prefix variable which ...', 'answers': '1', 'votes': '14', 'tags': 'python anaconda conda'}, {'question': 'Postgres and alembic - Assuming SERIAL sequence', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/56911833', 'summary': 'I have a postgres DB, which I manage through SQLAlchemy and alembic (for migrations). When creating a DB migration through alembic, I get the following INFO in the console. INFO [alembic.ddl....', 'answers': '1', 'votes': '14', 'tags': 'python postgresql flask alembic'}, {'question': "Using Pytorch's Multiprocessing along with Distributed", 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/56054164', 'summary': "I am trying to spawn a couple of process using pytorch's multiprocessing module within a openmpi distributed back-end. What I have is the following code: def run(rank_local, rank, world_size, maingp):...", 'answers': 0, 'votes': '14', 'tags': 'python pytorch openmpi'}, {'question': 'UWSGI does not redirect application stdout to stdout, only to file', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/55012664', 'summary': 'I have a Flask application running inside a container, where I have setup the logging with the StreamHandler(), so the logs are sent to stdout. When my uwsgi.ini file includes a statement to redirect ...', 'answers': 0, 'votes': '14', 'tags': 'python docker flask uwsgi'}, {'question': 'Grid data-structure and placement algorithm for my Battleships implementation?', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/50662071', 'summary': 'I am trying to make my own version of the game Battleships (in German: Schiffe versenken). I have made the game board as a 10x10 dataframe. The coordinates of the ships are created randomly. I have 4 ...', 'answers': '1', 'votes': '14', 'tags': 'python list pandas dataframe'}, {'question': 'Where does the nose.collector look for tests?', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/30282118', 'summary': "I want to use nose.collector as a test suite for setuptools, as described here. My package's source lives in mypackage/src, and I have tests in mypackage/tests. I have a setup.py that looks like this: ...", 'answers': '2', 'votes': '14', 'tags': 'python setuptools nose'}, {'question': 'Saving multiple images in MayaVi', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/24201190', 'summary': 'I want to render around 500 images and save them to different png files, therefore I wrote a small class which contains my dataset and a renderfunction from mayavi import mlab mlab.options.offscreen=...', 'answers': '1', 'votes': '14', 'tags': 'python mayavi'}, {'question': 'Gunicorn + nginx - Ignoring EPIPE', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/55768090', 'summary': 'I have an nginx-gunicorn-flask setup running on google compute and I keep getting the following from gunicorn: [2019-04-19 20:50:49 +0000] [3345] [DEBUG] POST / [2019-04-19 20:50:49 +0000] [3345] [...', 'answers': '3', 'votes': '14', 'tags': 'python nginx server gunicorn ubuntu-18.04'}]